<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ledgerback Research on </title>
    <link>/docs/mainsito/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ledgerback Research on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/mainsito/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/about/</guid>
      <description>About#Ledgerback Research is a 501(c)(3) worker cooperative and and decentralized research lab enacting the SDCI, a model for a knowledge ecosystem.
We study and build convergence (connection and integration) (emphasis on the alternative/decentralized internet), democratic ownership models, social technology, citizen-expertise, and tools for thought (TfT).
We produce open-access research (similarly to an academic or industry lab), including scientific publications, reports, blog posts, educational videos, open-source software, and demonstrations, and with these nurture the growth of researchers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/citations-mentions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/citations-mentions/</guid>
      <description>Citations &amp;amp; Mentions#Citations# Data Cooperatives, P2P Foundation Wiki  Mentions#October 2020#Journal Article | MDPI Sustainability#Calzada I., Platform and Data Co-Operatives amidst European Pandemic Citizenship. Sustainability 2020, 12, 8309.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/community/</guid>
      <description>Community#Ledgerback Research is a community for genuinely curious people who are interested in getting better at learning, sharing, researching, and building democratic ownership models, networked-scholarship, networked-culture, social technology, and tools for thought (TfT) (&amp;ldquo;Topics&amp;rdquo;).
To that end, the community building aspect of Ledgerback Research is creating a place to: 1) develop and train relevant skills for maturing into a researcher or maker, 2) find kindred spirits, friends and collaborators along the way, 3) produce serious research, 4) educate each other on interesting topics, and 5) give back to society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the Ledgerback Digital Commons Research Cooperative#Support Ledgerback Research&amp;rsquo;s work on:
 Educational content Research Tools Events  Credit/debit card#If you are an individual who would like to support our work, you can make a donation directly:
 Open Collective Donorbox  Direct Cryptocurrency Donation# BTC: TBA ETH: TBA  Afterward, contact us so we can thank you and send you a receipt for your records and tax purposes — and let us know us know if you&amp;rsquo;d like us to publicly thank you for your donation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/education/</guid>
      <description>Education#Our members create and curate educational materials on topics they find of interest.
Generally, these materials are created for self-study or summation of a member&amp;rsquo;s learning journey, or to be used by an instructor in their class.
Slides# Introduction to Commons-based Peer Production Micro-course Decentralized and Open Thinking Micro-course: Part 1 Introduction to Platform Cooperativism Micro-course: Part 1  School#The Coop plans to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/events/</guid>
      <description>Events#Meetings#Reading Group#We host a monthly meeting on the second Saturday of each month at 9 AM PST that covers readings in the reading group, primarily to learn about democratic ownership models, networked-scholarship, social technology, and tools for thought (TfT) (&amp;ldquo;Topics&amp;rdquo;) on Discord.Colloquium#We host a monthly meeting on the third Saturday of each month at 9 AM PST to discuss research updates and hear presentations on research, workflows, and projects on Discord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/flagship-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/flagship-project/</guid>
      <description>Flagship project#This page is under development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/jobs/</guid>
      <description>Jobs#Find jobs and opportunities here from across the convergent alternative internet (i.e., decentralized web).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/journal/</guid>
      <description>Journal#This page is under development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/library/</guid>
      <description>Library#Annotations#We store our annotations in Hypothesis.
Join our Hypothesis group and annotate documents across the web!
Bibliography#We store our bibliographies in Zotero.
Join our Zotero group and start adding to our ever-growing bibliography!
GitHub#Find our curated lists and digital gardens on GitHub.
Observatory#Work-in-progress
Glossary#Work-in-progress
Tools#Work-in-progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/members/</guid>
      <description>Members# Charles Adjovu Jack Smye Marvin Roman Joseph Tobing Darick Velasco Joshua Davila  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/membership/</guid>
      <description>Membership#To become a member, you must:
 complete our membership form, bring your own specific project in mind and with a commitment to presenting progress updates on it, and complete our orientation program.  Once we process your membership request as per our rules, you will receive an email from us.
We do not have any membership fees. However, members are subject to a non-refundable annual fee of $100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/merchandise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/merchandise/</guid>
      <description>Merchandise#Represent your industry with the LDCRC.
100% of proceeds will fund individuals &amp;amp; institutions through grants for fees, travel, research, projects, events, publishing &amp;amp; promotions.
  Redbubble (Merchandise)
 Shirts Stickers Hoodie    Teespring (Merchandise)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/networks/</guid>
      <description>Networks#Mentorship#Join our alternative internet mentorship network and start mentoring others or find a mentor to help your career.
Send an email to ledgerback@gmail.com answering these questions:
 Are you trying to become or find a mentor? Why are you interested in the mentorship network?  Consultants#Join our alternative internet consultants network and we&amp;rsquo;ll send relevant work requests your way. Alternatively, let us know what kind of project you have to tackle and our team will do our best to match you with expert consultants in our network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications#Writing#You can find our writings on:
 Medium LedgerbackHub  Newsletters#We have two (2) newsletters:
 Ledgerback Cooperative Distroid  Podcasts#You can find our podcast on Anchor.
Editorial Offer#Our editorial offer includes
 Access to all our archives and database. The opportunity to participate in our surveys and interact with our staff.  With the $100 of your subscription, you finance:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/questions/</guid>
      <description>Questions#Answered#1. What is social technology?... Social technology is the hardware and software that determine how we organize and collectively live our lives. But it is also the the ideas, knowledge, economics, and institutions that drive culture and sustain societies. And it is the way this knowledge is embedded in the technologies we use.
 2. What is a Tool for Thought(TfT)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/research/</guid>
      <description>Research#Approach#Under development.
Convergent# Convergence research is a means of solving vexing research problems, in particular, complex problems focusing on societal needs. It entails integrating knowledge, methods, and expertise from different disciplines and forming novel frameworks to catalyze scientific discovery and innovation. Convergence research is related to other forms of research that span disciplines - transdisciplinarity, interdisciplinarity, and multidisciplinarity. It is the closest to transdisciplinary research which was historically viewed as the pinnacle of evolutionary integration across disciplines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/services/</guid>
      <description>Services#We offer brainstorming and ideation services for products and collectives, question atomization, content writing, and publishing services.
You can find our services on Open Collective.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
