<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LDCRC on </title>
    <link>/docs/mainsito/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LDCRC on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/mainsito/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/about/</guid>
      <description>About#About us#Founded in 2018, Ledgerback Digital Commons Research Cooperative (LDCRC) is a 501(c)(3) member-led research nonprofit with a mission to shape the future for public benefit by investigating and appling emerging technologies while drawing attention towards human-centric futures.
The LDCRC works across fundamental research, tool-building, community-building, commercialization, and education to achieve our mission.
Ongoing Work#You can find out more about our ongoing work and writings in our Airtable base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/citations-and-mentions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/citations-and-mentions/</guid>
      <description>Citations and Mentions#Blockchain and the Rise of the Internet Cooperative#Cited by:
 Grounding Decentralised Technologies in Cooperative Principles: What Can &amp;lsquo;Decentralised Autonomous Organisations&amp;rsquo; (DAOs) and Platform Cooperatives Learn from Each Other?  Mentioned in:
 What We Learned from Our Research Sprint on Cooperative Data Governance  LDCRC#Mentioned in:
 Platform and Data Co-Operatives amidst European Pandemic Citizenship  A Preliminary Review of Blockchain in the Music Industry#Mentioned in:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/community/</guid>
      <description>Community#The LDCRC also supports and communicates about research and educational efforts on emerging technologies by offering office hours, a jobs board, awards, events, and media.
Office Hours#LDCRC&amp;rsquo;s weekly, pro-bono Office Hours provide the opportunity to receive one-on-one help with finding existing research, strategy, and/or general questions. Office Hours are held via Jitsi or Sprout video conferencing.
You can schedule a meeting here.
Librarians#Contact Charles Adjovu for help on finding existing research on a topic on emerging technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the Ledgerback Digital Commons Research Cooperative (LDCRC)#Support the LDCRC&amp;rsquo;s work on:
 Education Research Tools Community-building  How to donate#Credit/debit card#If you are an individual who would like to support our work, you can make a donation directly:
 Open Collective, Donorbox, or Every.org.  Direct Cryptocurrency Donation#You can directly donate cryptocurrency to the LDCRC on Every.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/education/</guid>
      <description>Education#We provide educational content and live sessions to help you make sense of emerging tehnologies, movements, and new imaginaries of the future.
Syllabi#Find syllabi on various topics.
Expect syllabi for our courses on Crypto &amp;amp; Cooperatives, Introduction to Data Cooperatives, and Introduction to Web3 to be added later to the site.
Introduction to Platform Cooperatives#Version 0.3
Lesson 1: Cooperative History and Enterprise Model#Cooperatives are people-centred enterprises owned, controlled and run by and for their members to realise their common economic, social, and cultural needs and aspirations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/faqs/</guid>
      <description>FAQs#Check out the FAQs table if you have any questions.
If your question is not mentioned in the table, send an email about your question to ledgerback@gmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/fundraisers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/fundraisers/</guid>
      <description>Fundraisers#The LDCRC is currently running fundraisers for:
 Fellowships: Fund a researcher to engage in independent research to help further our mission without perverse incentives Conference: Help us raise funds to run a conference covering a topic on emerging technologies, organizational forms, human-compatibel futures, independnet research, or another topic of interest, that can help connect the public with our members and other persons of interest Cloud Infrastructure: Help us pay for our cloud infrastructure costs so that we can provide more resources to our members to conduct their research Honors &amp;amp; Awards: Help us recognize individuals and organizations producing and sharing knowledge that helps us have a better understanding of the future  Additionally, the LDCRC plans to crowdfund for its projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/library/</guid>
      <description>Library#We’re aiming to assemble collections of academic and grey literature that would help people learn about emerging technologies and their implications for the future.
We have two main libraries, our Zotero library (primarily research literature) and our Portal database(primarily a curated list of resources about a field at the Ledgerback Frontier to help you learn the basics).
Portal#Currently, we have a curated list for Web3 that goes over the basics, and provides a critical review of claims in the Web3 field concerning decentralization, trustlessness, and other important concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/membership/</guid>
      <description>Membership#Become a lifetime member of the LDCRC for only $30.00. Our membership benefits include:
  governance rights (voting power, right to stand in an election, and right to participate in decision-making),
  access to member offers, such as discounts and special offers on goods and services (e.g., $5 discount on Distroid’s Paid Tier),
  access to exclusives (e.g., content, tools, cloud infrastructure, and data),</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/products-and-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/products-and-services/</guid>
      <description>Products &amp;amp; Services#In addition to our research, we also provide assistance to public and private organizations and individuals to learn and research about emerging technologies and how to find human-centric futures.
Products#Distroid Newsletter#The Distroid newsletter is a commentary and curated digest covering research, news, events, videos &amp;amp; podcasts, and more on emerging technologies and their implications for the future.
The Distroid newsletter&amp;rsquo;s paid tier includes both commentary and a curated digest of news, research, events, tools, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/research/</guid>
      <description>Research#Papers#A Preliminary Review of Blockchain in the Music Industry (November 6, 2018)# Musicians in the music industry are the primary content creators, and yet, have little to no control over their musical works after assigning their rights and management to third party intermediaries such as record labels, performance rights organizations, and publishers. Before the rise of file sharing platforms in the 1990s, this scenario was the norm for all musicians as record labels controlled nearly all facets of the music industry from musician funding to distribution and even royalty payment collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/subscribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/subscribe/</guid>
      <description>Subscribe#Subscribe to the LDCRC&amp;rsquo;s Substack newsletter to get updates sent directly to your email.
Subscribe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/translation/</guid>
      <description>Equitable Knowledge Transfer#Through our translation program, we will work on turning our research outputs the into products for the world to use, through various avenues (e.g., IP licensing, spin-offs). Through our translation program, we want to show that our research not only provides benefits to the public, but also has commercial value. Regarding the commercial value, we hope to translate our findings through equitable commercialization options such as cooperatives and trusts so that the value generated remains with the stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer#If you would like to help out, please refer to the volunteer board for tasks we need help with.
If you are interested in helping, please add your name and Twitter handle to the table via the link above.
Alternatively, you can fill out one of the roles below:
 Data Entry Content Editor Article Summarizer Grant Writer Event Organizer  Additionally, please consider becoming a curator for Distroid.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
