<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ledgerback Research on </title>
    <link>/docs/mainsito/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ledgerback Research on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/mainsito/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/about/</guid>
      <description>About#Founded in 2018, the Ledgerback Digital Commons Research Cooperative (LDCRC) is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit cooperative association coalescing a socially-aware expert community to advance knowledge in the decentralized web and related fields (i.e., the Ledgerback Frontier, the space between the current and the future ages of humanity).
Our outputs from our work can include scientific publications, reports, blog posts, open educational resources, trainings, tools, methods, platforms, open-source software, open datasets, newsletters, demonstrations, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/citations-and-mentions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/citations-and-mentions/</guid>
      <description>Citations &amp;amp; Mentions#Citations# Data Cooperatives, P2P Foundation Wiki  Mentions#October 2020#Journal Article | MDPI Sustainability#Calzada I., Platform and Data Co-Operatives amidst European Pandemic Citizenship. Sustainability 2020, 12, 8309.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/donate/</guid>
      <description>Donate to the Ledgerback Digital Commons Research Cooperative#Support the LDCRC&amp;rsquo;s work on:
 Educational content Research Tools Events Advocacy Trainings  How to donate#Credit/debit card#If you are an individual who would like to support our work, you can make a donation directly:
 Open Collective, Donorbox, or Every.org.  Direct Cryptocurrency Donation#You can directly donate cryptocurrency to the LDCRC on Every.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/events/</guid>
      <description>Events#Ongoing Events# Monthly Meetings every first Saturday of the month on Discord covering updates on the LDCRC and members.  Past Events# Creating Educational Materials on Platform Cooperativism  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/faqs/</guid>
      <description>Frequntly Asked Questions (FAQs)#Answered#1. What is social technology?... Social technology is the hardware and software that determine how we organize and collectively live our lives. But it is also the the ideas, knowledge, economics, and institutions that drive culture and sustain societies. And it is the way this knowledge is embedded in the technologies we use.
 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/flagship-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/flagship-project/</guid>
      <description>Projects#These member-led projects are currently under development:
 Observatory: An ecosystem mapping of people, events, language, concepts, databases, media, organizations, and more at the Ledgerback Frontier; Ledgerback Frontier Portal: A gateway to the Ledgerback Frontier (i.e., the Decentralized Web (DWeb) and related fields). The aim of the portal is to help people learn about and discover the Ledgerback Frontier through self-study resources (e.g., datasets, flashcards, quizzes); Bikestream: A project to encourage people to realize the value and benefits of managing their mobility data and micro-mobility vehicles, individually and collectively; DGov Score Framework: A project to develop a theoretical background on digital organizations and methods and tools for analyzing organizational concepts; Laplace: A project to develop an expertise network, knowledge graph, and content aggregator to encourage innovation and learning at the Ledgerback Frontier LedgerbackHub: a content library of thoughts and insights from members and friends on the Ledgerback Frontier; and Distroid: a monthly newsletter, with a focus on the convergence (connection and integration) of the decentralized web and related fields (Web3, Platform Cooperatives, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/jobs/</guid>
      <description>Jobs#Find jobs and other opportunities here from across the Ledgerback Frontier.
You can find a list of job boards in the Observatory&amp;rsquo;s JobBoards table</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/journal/</guid>
      <description>Journal#This page is under development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/members/</guid>
      <description>Members# Charles Adjovu  You can find Charles&amp;rsquo;s digital garden here   Jack Smye Marvin Roman Joseph Tobing Darick Velasco Joshua Davila  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/membership/</guid>
      <description>Membership#This page is under development as we update our Bylaws
Become a member of the LDCRC today!#All members have a voice in shaping the priorities of the LDCRC, sharing views and electing the Board of Directors. When you join as a Member, your support will help us to continue our current activities and establish amazing new projects.
Membership opens up the opportunity to deeply engage with the LDCRC in other ways; be the first to hear about our exciting projects, access exclusive information and resources, and take advantage of member rates on services and goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/office-hours/</guid>
      <description>Office Hours#LDCRC&amp;rsquo;s weekly, pro-bono Office Hours provide the opportunity to receive one-on-one help with finding existing research, strategy, and/or general questions. Office Hours are held via Jitsi or Sprout video conferencing.
Librarians#Contact Charles Adjovu for help on finding existing research on a topic under the Ledgerback Frontier.
Charles&amp;rsquo;s Hours#Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday, 3pm–10pm PST Max time per person: 30 mins
Good questions for Charles:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/outputs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/outputs/</guid>
      <description>Outputs#Papers# Cooperative, Ledgerback, A Preliminary Review of Blockchain in the Music Industry (November 6, 2018). Available at SSRN: https://ssrn.com/abstract=3280838 or http://dx.doi.org/10.2139/ssrn.3280838  Musicians in the music industry are the primary content creators, and yet, have little to no control over their musical works after assigning their rights and management to third party intermediaries such as record labels, performance rights organizations, and publishers. Before the rise of file sharing platforms in the 1990s, this scenario was the norm for all musicians as record labels controlled nearly all facets of the music industry from musician funding to distribution and even royalty payment collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/portal/</guid>
      <description>Ledgerback Frontier Portal#The Ledgerback Frontier Portal is a gateway to the thought spaces at the Ledgerback Frontier, the space between the present and future ages of humanity, exemplified by the Decentralized Web (DWeb) and related fields. The aim of the portal is to help people understand how people are thinking or conceptualizing these fields through self-study resources (primarily, through foundational reading lists).
You can find the Frontier Portal’s repository for self-study resources on Web3 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications#Ongoing#We have three ongoing publications:
 LedgerbackHub, Distroid, and Ledgerback Podcast.  Our long-form writing is on the LedgerbackHub, but may also be found on Medium
The Distroid newsletter is a monthly newsletter, with a focus on the convergence (connection and integration) of the decentralized web and related fields (Web3, Platform Cooperatives, etc.) (i.e., the fields of the Ledgerback Frontier).
The LedgerbackHub is a content library of thoughts and insights from members and friends on the Ledgerback Frontier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/research-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/research-advice/</guid>
      <description>Research Advice#Some resources to help you get started with independent research and researching the Ledgerback Frontier.
Guides# Open Scientist Handbook Internet Search Tips from Gwern.net Social Science Research Guide by Dr. Robert V. Labaree Introduction to College Research  Tools# Kausalflow tool directory  Also refer to the Ledgerback Scholar Toolbox and Guide (LSTG).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/research/</guid>
      <description>Research#Here you will find requests for research and early-stage concepts, and some helpful approaches to researching the Ledgerback Frontier.
Approach#Here are a list of research approaches that can help navigate the Ledgerback Frontier:
 Convergent Research Exploratory Research  Convergent Research# Convergence research is a means of solving vexing research problems, in particular, complex problems focusing on societal needs. It entails integrating knowledge, methods, and expertise from different disciplines and forming novel frameworks to catalyze scientific discovery and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/store/</guid>
      <description>Store#Welcome to the LDCRC&amp;rsquo;s store. Here, you will find merchandise, courses, certifications, and more.
Merchandise#Support the LDCRC by purchasing some LDCRC-branded merchandise.
 Redbubble  Shirts Stickers Hoodies   Teespring  Stickers Shirts Hoodies    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/trainings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/trainings/</guid>
      <description>Trainings#Our members from time to time offer training and online learning sessions on a matter of their interest on the Ledgerback Frontier.
2022#Our expected training programs for 2022 are:
 Exploring the Ledgerback Frontier  Exploring the Ledgerback Frontier#Four sessions in the training program will be offered in early 2022.
You can find the sessions listed below.
 Basics of Web3 Basics of Platform Cooperativism Basics of Research on Decentralized Web (DWeb) Blockchain Cooperatives: The intersection of Cooperativism and Web3  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/mainsito/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/mainsito/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer Board#If you would like to help out, please refer to the volunteer board for tasks we need help with.
If you are interested in helping, please add your name and Twitter handle to the table via the link above.
Alternatively, you can fill out one of the roles below:
 Data Entry Video Editor Audio Editor Article Summarizer Grant Writer Systems Administrator Research Assistant Software Developer Community Manager Communications manager Operations manager Event Organizer UI/UX Designer Social Media Manager  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
